

PANAWAT JAROENKHET

Address: Khonkaen, Thailand Facebook: Jan Tor

Email: pnwat.ja@gmail.com

Github:tortor1011

Positions Developer (Internship, traineeship)

Website: panawatjantor.com

SUMMARY

Hi, My name is Tor. This year, I'm 21 years old and studying at Khonkaen University, and I'm looking for an internship that will help me gain experience in my first job. I'm a highly adaptable person who loves to do a job and learn new skills. I have been prepared for programming since 3 years ago, and now I have dexterity for a while, I also have English communication skills which can help me have less complicated conversations when I hit a language wall.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kku stock photo organized (In progress)

2024 - Present

making KKU Stock Photos Web Application for KKU users and everyone who wants to achieve a
picture from Khonkaen University.

MJ Petshop Website 2024

• Development website for pet shop manage product information.

Cocoamore Website 2024

• Development website for helping cafeteria about digital management.

Technician Mobilib KKU 2022 — 2024

• Technician-Developer in Mobilib organization support for various equipment and Deverloping.

iTalk6-Operation Team

2024

- Responsible for controlling the sound room and controlling video.
- Procure and inspect equipment for the location

iSchool Kickoff 2023 2023

- Procure and inspect equipment for the location
- Compare contact coordination equipment equipment

EDUCATION

B.i.S: Bachelor of Information Science

(2022- Present)

Faculty of Humanities and Social Sciences Khonkaen University

- · bachelor degree
- · Information Science

Strisuksa School (2016 - 2022)

High school

- English International Programs
- Science-Computer Programs

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

skill (basic levels) Dexerity (Sort by high to low) Languages: English in Intermediate Level

Php Vs code
Python Canva Speak (
Html Premiere Pro Listen (

Css Figma
Javascript Draw.io
Photoshop

Listen Read Write

Technical Skills: IT Work(Pc building, Hardware knowledge, etc)